[EP08]
But she chose me, didn't she?
Su Hong,
I sent you here
because you're her brother.
Don't push your luck.
My brother is on my side.
It's only right.
Get some rest.
Don't worry about anything else.
I'll always be on your side.
Brother.
Let go of me.
Chu Nanfeng.
What did I touch yesterday?
Tell me.
What exactly did I touch?
You want to kill me.
You said that
if I want to kill someone,
I should put it here.
You think I won't dare?
You owe me a life.
Oh.
Your mother committed suicide.
What does it have to do with me?
Let's divorce.
Divorce?
Are you going to find Chu Nanfeng?
You don't kill Boren,
but he dies because of you.
I can't stay with you anymore.
Is this reason
enough?
Fine.
I'll kill Hongxiu right now.
And
this
is the letter your mother left.
I'll just tear it up.
Give it to me.
Let's play a game.
I'll give you three days
to find this gun
and get it.
Otherwise,
I'll burn the letter.
Bah!
Who would play such a boring game with you?
My dear,
everything in this world comes with conditions.
If you want something,
you have to fight for it.
Will you play?
Yes.
[Where could Ling Shenxing have hidden the gun?]
Nothing here.
What are you doing in my study so early?
[Oh, no.]
[He found me.]
Young Marshal.
You're up so early.
Well,
I'm looking for a book
to pass the time.
I don't have
anything to entertain you.
Behave yourself.
[I searched the Ling family but found no gun.]
[It must be with Ling Shenxing.]
[Ling Shenxing,]
[I don't believe so much knockout drops]
[can't make you dizzy.]
Young Marshal,
you haven't rested yet.
I've prepared a tranquilizing tea for you.
Put it down.
[Ling Shenxing]
[is still pretending to be aloof.]
That's not gonna work.
Forget it.
I'll go all out.
Young Marshal,
this tea
is specially made for you.
You've been working so hard.
This tea
is good for your health.
I'm in good health.
I don't need it.
What are you up to?
Cousin.
I saw your study light is still on.
Miss Su is here too.
[What is she doing here?]
[Such a bad timing.]
[My plan is going to be ruined.]
When you were studying abroad,
you got used to drinking
to help you sleep.
I'm afraid
he's not used to tea.
Miss Su,
you seem to know little about him.
Cousin,
I brought this liquor from abroad.
I guess you must like it.
[She's trying to steal him.]
[If you take the tea away,]
[my plan will be ruined.]
Don't bother, Miss Ye.
This tea
is specially prepared for Young Marshal.
He won't like this tea.
Cousin
I'm sorry.
I just think
Miss Su may not know your habits.
I didn't mean it.
Miss Su
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I'm sleepy.
I wanna sleep.
The tea
is better to drink when it's hot.
Young Marshal,
have a good rest.
I'll leave you to it.
Ye Jinrou,
you made a strong cup of green tea.
Wait and see.
I must get back
my mother's will.
Good night.
Good.
You're back, Miss.
What?
My mother wrote to me?
This is the letter from the Madam.
She also said that you should try to be
the third wife of the Marshal.
The third wife?
Is she insane?
A man over fifty,
why doesn't she marry him?
How could she be my mother?
Get out!
Young Marshal.
Ling Shenxing,
you did drink the tranquilizer tea.
Piece of cake.
I can handle this.
The drug works well.
Ling Shenxing is sleeping like a log.
Then
I can get the gun.
He's still not awake.
He's annoying,
but he's good-looking.
What are you thinking about?
Focus on the task at hand.
The gun is not in the pocket of the clothes.
Does he carry the gun
even when he sleeps?
I knew it.
Childish.
When did you wake up?
Young Marshal, keep your word.
I got the gun.
You should fulfill your promise.
You want to kill me.
Let me go.
Give me the suicide note.
What if I say no?
You think I dare not kill you?
I thought you would say,
my life
for your mother's,
we're even.
Come on.
I'll teach you how to shoot.
Put your hand
on it.
Pull the bolt.
Then,
keep your wrist steady.
Aim at this.